<resources>
    <string name="app_name">DailyPsalm</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string-array name="psalms">
        <item> BLESSED is the man\n
                                    Who walks not in the counsel\n
                                        the ungodly,\n
                                    Nor stands in the path of\n
                                        sinners,\n
                                 2\t  But his delight is in the law of\n
                                        the lord,\n
                                    And inHis law he meditates\n
                                        day and night.\n
                        3\t\t\t\t\t\t\tHe shall be like a tree\n
                                      Plated by the rivers of\n
                                        water,\n
                                      That brings forth its fruit in its\n
                                        season,\n
                                      Whose leaf also shall not\n
                                        wither;\n
                                    And whatever he does shall\n
                                        prosper.\n\n
                        4\t\t\t\t\t The ungodly are not so,\n
                                    But are like the chaff which the\n
                                        wind drives away.\n
                        5\t\t\t\t\t Therefor the ungodly shall not\n
                                        stand in the judgment,\n
                                    Nor sinners in the congregation of\n
                                        the righteous.\n\n\n
                        6\t\t\t\t\t For the Lord knows the way of\n
                                        the righteous.\n
                                    But the way of the ungodly shall\n
                                        perish.\n



        </item>
        <item name="psalm_two">\n\n
           WHY do the nations rage,\n
             And the people plot a vain\n
               thing?\n
           The Kings of the earth set \n
               themselves,
           And the rulers take counsel\n
                together,\n
           Against the Lord and against His\n
                Anointed,saying,\n
           "Let us break Their bonds in\npieces\n
            And cast away Their cords from\n us."\n\n

           He who sits in the heavens\n
                shall laugh;\n
           The Lord shall hold them in\n
                derision.\n
           Then He shall speak to them in\n
                His wrath,\n
           And distress them in his deep\n
                displeasure:\n
           "Yet I have set My King On My\n
            holy hill of Zion."\n\n

            "I will declare the decree:
            The Lord has said to Me,\n
            'You are My Son,\n
            Today I have begotten You,\n
            Ask of Me, andI will give You\n
            The Nations for Your inheritance,\n
            And the ends of the earth for Your \n
                possession.\n
            You shall break them with a rod\n
                of iron\n
            The Lord Our Shield\n
             You shall dash them to pieces like a potter's vessel.'"\n\n

            Now therefore, be wise, O lings;\n
            Be instructed, you judges of the \n
                earth.\n
            Serve the Lord with fear,\n
            And rejoice with trembling.\n
            Kiss the Son, lest He be angry,\n
            And you perish in the way,\n
            when His wrath is kindled but a little.\n
            Blessed are all those who put their\n
            trust in Him\n
        </item>
        <item name="psalm_three">
            A Psalm of David when he fled from Absalom his son\n
            LORD, how they have increased\n
                who troubled me!\n
            Many are they who rise  up against me\n
            Many are they who say of me\n
            "There is no help for him God"\n\n

            But You, O Lord,are a shield for me\n
            My Glory and the One who lifts\n
                up my head.\n
            I cried to the Lord with my voice,\n
            and He heard me from His holy hill\n\n

            I lay down and slept;\n
            I awoke, for the Lord sustained\n
                me\n
            I will not be afraid of ten\n
                thousand of people\n
            Who have set themselves against\n
            me all around.\n\n

            Arise, O Lord;\n
            Save me, O my God!\n
            For You have struck all my\n
                enemies on the cheekbone;\n
            You have broken the teeth of the\n
                ungodly.\n
            Salvation belongs to the Lord.\n
            Your blessing is upon Your\n
                people\n

        </item>
        <item name="psalm_four">
            1 Answer me when I call to you, my righteous God.\n
            Give me relief from my distress; have mercy on\n
                me and hear my prayer.\n
            2 How long will you people turn my glory into shame?\n
            How long will you love delusions and seek false gods\n
            3 Know that the LORD has set apart\n
                his faithful servant for himself;\n
            the LORD hears when I call to him.\n
            4 Tremble and do not sin; when you\n
                are on your beds, search your hearts and be silent.\n
            5 Offer the sacrifices of the righteous\n
                and trust in the LORD. 6 Many, LORD, are asking,\n
            “Who will bring us prosperity?” Let the light of your\n
                face shine on us.\n
            7 Fill my heart with joy when their grain and new wine abound.\n
            8 In peace I will lie down and sleep,\n
                for you alone, LORD, make me dwell in safety.
        </item>
        <item name="psalm_five">
            For the director of music. For pipes. A psalm of David.\n
            1 Listen to my words, LORD, consider my lament.\n
            2 Hear my cry for help,\n
                my King and my God, for to you I pray.\n
            3 In the morning, LORD, you hear my voice;\n
                in the morning I lay my requests before you\n
              and wait expectantly.\n
            4 For you are not a God who is pleased with wickedness;\n
                with you, evil people are not welcome.\n
            5 The arrogant cannot stand in your presence.\n
                You hate all who do wrong;\n
            6 you destroy those who tell lies.\n
              The bloodthirsty and deceitful you, LORD, detest.\n
            7 But I, by your great love, can come into your house;\n
              in reverence I bow down toward your holy temple.\n
            8 Lead me, LORD, in your righteousness\n
                because of my enemies— make your way straight before me.\n
            9 Not a word from their mouth can be trusted;\n
                their heart is filled with malice.\n
              Their throat is an open grave; with their tongues\n
              they tell lies.\n
            10 Declare them guilty, O God! Let their intrigues\n
               be their downfall. Banish them for their many sins,\n
               for they have rebelled against you.\n
            11 But let all who take refuge in you be glad;\n
               let them ever sing for joy. Spread your protection\n
               over them, that those who love your name may rejoice in you.\n
            12 Surely, LORD, you bless the righteous;\n
               you surround them with your favor as with a shield.\n
        </item>

        <item name="psalm_six">
            For the director of music. With stringed instruments.
            According to sheminith. A psalm of David.
            1 LORD, do not rebuke me in your
                anger or discipline me in your wrath.
            2 Have mercy on me, LORD, for I am faint;
                heal me, LORD, for my bones are in agony.
            3 My soul is in deep anguish.
                How long, LORD, how long?
            4 Turn, LORD, and deliver me;
                save me because of your unfailing love.
            5 Among the dead no one proclaims your name.
                Who praises you from the grave?
            6 I am worn out from my groaning.
                All night long I flood my bed with weeping
                and drench my couch with tears.
            7 My eyes grow weak with sorrow;
                they fail because of all my foes.
            8 Away from me, all you who do evil,
                for the LORD has heard my weeping.
            9 The LORD has heard my cry for mercy;
                the LORD accepts my prayer.
            10 All my enemies will be overwhelmed
                with shame and anguish; they will
                turn back and suddenly be put to shame.
        </item>
        <item name="psalm_seven">
            1 A Meditation of David, which he sang to the Lord
            concerning the words of Cush,
            a Benjamite. O Lord my God, in You I put my trust;
               Save me from all those who persecute me; And deliver me,
            2 Lest they tear me like a lion, Rending
            me in pieces, while there is none to deliver.
            3 O Lord my God, if I have done this:
            If there is iniquity in my hands,
            4 If I have repaid evil to him who was at peace with me,
            Or have plundered my enemy without cause,
            5 Let the enemy pursue me and overtake me;
            Yes, let him trample my life to the earth,
            And lay my honor in the dust. Selah
            6 Arise, O Lord, in Your anger; Lift Yourself up
             because of the rage of my enemies;
            Rise up for me to the judgment You have commanded!
            7 So the congregation of the peoples shall surround You;
            For their sakes, therefore, return on high.
            8 The Lord shall judge the peoples; Judge me,
            O Lord, according to my righteousness,
            And according to my integrity within me.
            9 Oh, let the wickedness of the wicked come to an end,
            But establish the just; For the righteous God tests the hearts and minds.
            10 My defense is of God, Who saves the upright in heart.
            11 God is a just judge, And God is angry with the wicked every day.
            12 If he does not turn back, He will sharpen His sword; He bends His bow and makes it ready.
            13 He also prepares for Himself instruments of death; He makes His arrows into fiery shafts.
            14 Behold, the wicked brings forth iniquity; Yes, he conceives trouble and brings forth falsehood.
            15 He made a pit and dug it out, And has fallen into the ditch which he made.
            16His trouble shall return upon his own head, And his violent dealing shall come down on his own crown.
            17 I will praise the Lord according to His righteousness, And will sing praise to the name of the Lord Most High.


        </item>
    </string-array>



</resources>
